hostpilot.com 2003-08-22

# Intermedia.NET - Legal: Legal & Policies

**Purpose**

Intermedia.NET, Inc. has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for Intermedia.NET, Inc. websites, including intermedia.net, deskpilot.com, hostpilot.com, 0effort.com and all sub-domains under these domains. Scope

This privacy statement only covers the information collected on Intermedia.NET's web sites. The Intermedia.NET's web sites contain links to other sites. Intermedia.NET is not responsible for the privacy practices, actions, or the content of such web sites. 

**Children's Guidelines**

Intermedia.NET requires that all account holders be 18 years of age or older. Children are not provided access to any Intermedia.NET services in which any personal data is collected beyond the collection of a visitor's IP address and session status. 

If Intermedia.NET becomes aware that any child has accessed Intermedia.NET's non-publicly available web sites, the account through which the child has gained access will be terminated.

No information should be submitted to or posted at Intermedia.NET web sites by persons under 13 years of age. Intermedia.NET does not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13. All Intermedia.NET services are open only to persons over the age of 18.

If you believe Intermedia.NET has collected any information from or about anyone under 13, please contact us immediately at [ privacy@intermedia.net](mailto:privacy@intermedia.net).

**Information Collection**

Our web sites use on-line order forms for customers to request services. Through these order forms we collect your contact information and financial information. Your contact information from the order forms is used to contact you regarding the status of your account and to send you information about Intermedia.NET services available. Financial information that we collect from you is used to bill you for your Intermedia.NET account services.

Intermedia.NET, Inc. web sites also log IP addresses and other user session information to help diagnose problems with our servers, to administer and improve our web sites, to facilitate marketing of Intermedia.NET products, and to gather broad demographic and statistical information. 

**Cookies**

Intermedia.NET web sites use cookies to retain your session state during your logon to the HostPilot® Control Panel. You may opt out of the use of cookies by turning them off in your web browser. However, the use of cookies is necessary for the use of Intermedia.NET's HostPilot® Control Panel.

**Public Forums**

Intermedia.NET sites make chat rooms, forums, message boards, and news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.

**Information Dissemination**

Intermedia.NET will release personally identifiable information about you as is reasonably necessary for the provision of Intermedia.NET services for which you have subscribed. This includes, but is not limited to:

  * provision of financial information to organizations such as VeriSign, PaymenTech, Signio and CyberCash for Intermedia.NET billing purposes, 
  * provision of contact and software usage information to our software license providers for the purpose of software licensing compliance, licensing usage calculation, and billing purposes 
  * provision of your account information to independent contractors providing services in support of Intermedia.NET's delivery of services to you. (Note: all independent contractors to whom Intermedia.NET provides account information are required to sign a non-disclosure agreement). 
  * transfer information that you provide to apply for separate software licenses through Intermedia.NET such as Miva Merchant. The information you provide to Intermedia.NET to apply for separate software licenses or directly to the software licensor will be subject to the privacy policy of the licensor and not this Privacy Policy. 

In addition, Intermedia.NET may release personally identifiable information necessary for the prosecution or defense of any legal claim or right to which Intermedia.NET is a party. Intermedia.NET will also release personally identifiable information as required by law. 

**Security**

Intermedia.NET's web sites have security measures in place to protect against the loss, misuse, or alteration of the information under our control. Your contact and financial information is submitted via a secure (HTTPS) connection and stored in the Intermedia.NET, Inc. database protected by a firewall. Access to your information is restricted to authorized Intermedia.NET, Inc. personnel and contracting partners only.

**Contacting the Web Sites, Opting-out, Deactivating Your Account**

If you wish to terminate your account or opt-out of receiving communications from Intermedia.NET which are not reasonably necessary for the provision of services to you, please contact Intermedia.NET at the address below. You may also revise your contact and financial information or terminate your account through the HostPilot® Control Panel.

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the privacy practices of our web sites, or your dealings with Intermedia.NET's web sites, you may contact:

Intermedia.NET Legal  
800 California Street, Suite 200  
Mountain View, California 94041  

**Updates to Privacy Policy**

Intermedia.NET, Inc. reserves the right to change these policies at any time. Any changes to the privacy policy will be posted at the web sites.

Copyright © Intermedia.NET, Inc. 2001. All Rights Reserved.

Users of this site agree to be bound by the Intermedia.NET Service Agreement, Service Level Agreement, and acceptable use policies.
